Thaddeus W. Maliszewski collection CPAA 86.04
Connecticut Polish American Archives, Elihu Burritt Library, Central Connecticut State University
- Polish American Congress (PAC)
  - Polish Junior League of Connecticut - Menuet Bal, 1968-1972: Photos, clippings, souvenir booklet. (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Polish Junior League Day - Governor's Proclamation, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 14A)
  - R. Eibel- Polish sailor and INS, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - PAC CT- Incorporation, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - PAC CT- Two photos of PAC officials, including Maliszewski, 1958-1967 (Box 4, Folder 16A)
  - PAC CT- Pulaski Day parade plans, 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Pulaski Day, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Pulaski Day, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Pulaski Day, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Pulaski Day, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Pulaski Day, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Newspaper clippings of interest to Polish American Congress, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - PAC CT- Correspondence, articles, 1962-1964 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - PAC CT- Correspondence, articles, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - PAC Millennium Committee- Book Committee: Acknowledgements from School Libraries for donation of Halecki's A History of Poland, 1966-1968 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - PAC, Millennium Committee - Book Committee: Newspaper clippings, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - PAC, Millennium Committee- Military Ball January 1966 - correspondence (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - PAC, Millennium Committee- Military Ball January 1966 - finances (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - PAC, Millennium Committee- Military Ball January 1966 - arrangements (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - PAC, Millennium Committee- Military Ball January 1966 - program (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - PAC, Millennium Committee- Military Ball January 1966 - invitations and responses (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - PAC, Millennium Committee- Military Ball January 1966 - liability insurance (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - PAC, Millennium Committee- Military Ball January 1966 - contracts (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - PAC, Millennium Committee- Military Ball January 1966 - tickets (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - PAC, Millennium Committee- Military Ball January 1966 - newspaper clippings and other publicity (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - PAC, District of Conn.- Millennium Manifesto, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - PAC, Millennium Committee- Presidential Proclamation, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - PAC, Millennium Committee- Photographs, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - PAC, Millennium Committee- Book Committee - correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - PAC, Millennium Committee- Book Committee - finances, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - PAC, Millennium Committee- Book Committee - Acknowledgements - Public & Private libraries, Halecki's History of Poland, 1966-1968 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - PAC, Millennium Committee- District of Connecticut finances, 1966-1969 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - PAC, Millennium Committee- History of Connecticut Polonia 1966-1969. (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - PAC, Millennium Committee- Biuletyn Informacyjny, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - PAC, Millennium Committee- Other historical events: “The Polish Millenium- its Significance and Relevance to us”; pamphlets; bulletins, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - PAC, Millennium Committee- Special events, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - PAC, Millennium Committee- Commemorative Stamp/Medallions, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - PAC, Millennium Committee- Membership, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - PAC, Millennium Committee- Subcommittee, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - PAC Millenium Celebration - District of Conn., Millennium Committee - meetings/correspondence, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Pulaski submarine launching, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Commemoration of Polish Constitution Day, May 3, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - PAC Millennium Committee- District Of Connecticut- reports, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - PAC Millennium Committee- District Of Connecticut- finances, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - PAC Millennium Committee- Pulaski Day arrangements, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - PAC Millennium Committee- Governor's Proclamation, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - PAC Millennium Committee- Congressional Resolution and other declarations, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - PAC Millennium Committee- Programs and Memorabilia, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - PAC Millennium Committee- Speeches and reports, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - PAC Millennium Committee- Newspaper clippings, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - CT PAC- Millenium Banquet at Hotel America, Hartford, October 10, 1965. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - CT PAC- Millenium celebration- Bushnell Concert, May 15, 1966. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Millenium celebration newspaper clippings, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Millenium celebration- Dozynki, August 14, 1966. (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Millenium celebration- Bushnell Concert, December 4, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Millenium Washington Banquet and Stamp, July 30, 1966. (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - PAC Millennium Committee- Pulaski Day- correspondence, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - PAC District of Conn.- Correspondence, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - PAC District of Conn.- Correspondence; Statement of cash receipts and disbursements, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - PAC District of Conn.- Correspondence; handwritten notes, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - PAC District of Conn.– Finances, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - PAC District of Conn.– Handwritten list of books, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - PAC District of Conn.- 25th Anniversary of Battle of Monte Cassino, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - PAC District of Conn.- Pulaski Day- Proclamation; Parade orders, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - PAC District of Conn.– Correspondence, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - PAC District of Conn.– Connecticut Philatelic Exhibition (Connpex), 1968 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - PAC- Karol Cardinal Wojtyla's visit to New Britain, CT, September 18, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - PAC- District of Conn.- Political interests, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - PAC- District of Conn.- Annual Convention, February 23, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - PAC- District of Conn.- Association of Polish Priests in CT - May 4th Celebration, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - PAC- District of Conn.- Pulaski Day Parade, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - PAC- District of Conn.- Dinner Dance Program - October 19, 1969 (There is no Folder 30) (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - PAC- District of Conn.- Emblem, circa 1969 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - PAC- District of Conn.- "Candidates Answers to Polish Americans": press release, election, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - PAC- District of Conn.- 50th Anniversary of the Warsaw Battle, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - PAC- District of Conn.- Pulaski Day Parade, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - PAC- District of Conn.- Correspondence, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - PAC- District of Conn.- 8th Annual Convention, Feb. 22, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - PAC- District of Conn.- Correspondence, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - PAC- District of Conn.- By-laws, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - PAC- District of Conn.– Government paperwork, correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - PAC- District of Conn.- Membership List, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - PAC- District of Conn.– Meeting documents, 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - PAC- District of Conn.- President's Report, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - PAC- District of Conn.- Committee Reports/Sprawozdanie, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - PAC- District of Conn.- "We Love America Picnic", September 19, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - PAC- District of Conn.- Pulaski Day Parade, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - PAC- District of Conn.- Finances, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - PAC- District of Conn.- Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - PAC- District of Conn.– Committee (handwritten notes), 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - PAC- District of Conn.- Polish American Bicentennial Committee, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - PAC- District of Conn.- Election of officers, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - PAC- District of Conn.- Membership Drive, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - PAC- District of Conn.- Hartford Public Schools memorandums & resolutions, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - PAC- District of Conn.- Hartford Area Manpower Planning Council, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - PAC- District of Conn.- "Katyn Forest Massacre", 1975 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - PAC- District of Conn.- General Casimir Pulaski Monument, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - PAC- District of Conn.- Information Center for Eastern Europeans in the Greater Hartford Area, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - PAC- District of Conn.- Daniel Patrick Kuzia vs. Heritage Society, Inc., 1976 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - PAC- District of Conn.- Stanley Kokoska Affair, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - PAC- District of Conn.- H.R. 71(First Ammendment Restoration Act) Compensation for Polish and Czech Army Veterans, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - PAC- District of Conn.- Political Action Committee, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - PAC- District of Conn.- By-laws, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - PAC- District of Conn.- Pulaski Parade, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - PAC- District of Conn.– Bulletins, correspondence, 1977-1981 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - PAC- District of Conn.– President’s reports, 1980-1982 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - PAC- District of Conn.- Rejection of 3 new members, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - PAC- District of Conn.– President’s report, correspondence, 1984; articles, 1986, 1984-1986 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - PAC- District of Conn.- Report of the Auditing Committee, re: Solidarity Fund Raising Committee, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - PAC- District of Conn.- Pulaski Day Parade, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Pulaski Bicentennial Committee of Connecticut, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - PAC- Related correspondence, 1977-1981 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Polish Americans - Appointments by Carter Administration, 1977-1981 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - President Carter's visit in Poland; clippings, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Radio Free Europe/Radio Liberty- Correspondence, essays, reports, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Various publications (local and international), 1949-1978 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - PAC Incorporated: Its History and Objectives, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - PAC- National Meeting, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - PAC- Board of Directors Meeting, Chicago, December, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - PAC- Sixth National Convention, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - PAC- Newspaper clippings, National Meeting, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - PAC- National meeting- Protokol, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - PAC- Pulaski Day Parade- New York City, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - PAC- Millennium Committee- New York, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - PAC- Reports, proceedings, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - PAC- National meeting minutes (Protokol), 1966 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - PAC- National meeting report (Srawozdanie), 1966 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - PAC- National meeting minutes (Protokol), 1967 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper clippings regarding millennium, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - PAC- President Mazewski report October-December, 1968. (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - PAC- National Office correspondence, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - PAC- Board of Directors Meeting And 7th National Convention, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - PAC- Resolutions, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - PAC- "Czas" controversy, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - PAC- Newspaper clippings, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - PAC- Newspaper clippings, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - PAC- Vice president Edward Kurmel's affair, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - PAC- Edward J. Tomasik - candidate for PAC president- flyers, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - K. Rozmarek's statements to the Republican and Democratic platform Committees, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - The National Association of Polish Americans, et al. vs. The Polish American Congress, et al., 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - PAC- Board of Directors meeting, August, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - PAC- National Meeting- Resolutions and Amendments to the Constitution, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - PAC- National Finances, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - PAC- Form/document (blank), 1968 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - PAC- National Meeting- Reports and Speeches, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - PAC- National Meeting- Minutes, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - PAC- National Meeting- Delegates credentials, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - PAC- National Meeting- Newspaper clippings, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - PAC- Conference of Intellectuals of Polish Ancestry, June 27-28, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - PAC- 25th Anniversary, Washington D.C., July 26, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - PAC- Resolutions, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - PAC- Board of Directors Meeting; 8th National Convention, Chicago, Illinois, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - PAC- National – “Protokol Osmej Krajowej Konwencji KPA”, President's Mazewski speech, news clippings, Chicago, Illinois, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 36A)
  - PAC- Chairmen of Commissions, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - PAC- By-laws, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - PAC- International Affairs, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - PAC- Finances, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - PAC- Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - PAC- Reports, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - PAC- Minutes, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Tomasik Edward– “Wisconsin Plan” Committee – Publicity, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - PAC- Newspaper clippings, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - PAC- Advisory Council to the President on Educational and Cultural Affairs April, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - PAC- Ethnicity, Discrimination and Anti-Defamation, 1969-1971 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - PAC- National Meeting- By-laws, committees, panels, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - PAC- National Meeting - Reports and Speeches, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - PAC- National Meeting- Programs and Pamphlets, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - PAC- National Meeting- Delegate credentials for TWM, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - PAC- National Meeting- Newspaper clippings, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - PAC- Anti-Defamation Civic Alertness Commission, 1970-1979 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - PAC- National Meeting- Reports and speeches, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - PAC- National Meeting- Resolutions and delegations, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - PAC- National Meeting– Committees, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - PAC- National Meeting- Pamphlets and programs, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - PAC- National Meeting- Delegates credentials, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - PAC- National Meeting– Correspondence, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - PAC- National Meeting- Statement to Jimmy Carter Democratic Nominee, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - PAC- National Meeting- Legionnaire Disease, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - PAC- National Meeting- Agenda, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - PAC- National Meeting- Newspaper clippings, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - PAC- Central Office Material- Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - PAC- Central Office Material- By-laws, 1972-1978 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - PAC- Central Office Material- Pulaski Day, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - PAC- Central Office Material- Board of Directors Meeting, January 16-17, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - PAC- Central Office Material- Board of Directors Meeting, June 18-19, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - PAC- Central Office Material- President Aloysius A. Mazewski- Speeches, articles, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - PAC- Central Office Material- U.S. President Gerald R. Ford - Campaign issues, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - PAC- Central Office Material- 10th National Convention, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - PAC- Central Office Material- National Directors Report (TWM), 1976 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - PAC- Central Office Material- National Vice-President Nomination (TWM), 1976 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - PAC- Central Office Material- News releases, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - PAC- Central Office Material- Newspaper clippings, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - PAC- Conference of Polonia's status in political affairs of the Republic, December 14, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - PAC- Newspaper clippings, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - PAC- Documents related to problems in Poland, financial paperwork, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - PAC- Board of Directors Meeting, committee descriptions, central office correspondence, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - List of Polish-American Organizations (by state), 1976 (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - Polonia '78- Polonia Jutra- Toronto, Canada- Pamphlets, programs, and advertisements, May 20-28, 1978. (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Polonia '78- Newspaper clippings- Polonia Jutra, Toronto, Canada, May 20-28, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Polonia '78- Polonia Jutra, Toronto, Canada- Correspondence, agendas, speeches, and reports, May 20-28, 1978. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - PAC National Headquarters- Correspondence, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - PAC- Pulaski stamp– Newspaper clippings, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - PAC- Pulaski Stamp– Correspondence, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Polish American Day Conference- News coverage- U.S. State Department, October 5, 1978. (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Polish American Day Conference– Correspondence, research, October 5, 1978. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - PAC- Follow up activity- Polish American Day conference, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - PAC- Report of the President- Correspondence, financial documents, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - “The Invisible Generation” by S. Blejwas, in New Horizon, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - PAC- Statement of Aloysius A. Mazewski, Summary of Executive Committee meeting, Meeting with President Carter, minutes of Board of Directors meeting, correspondence, financial report, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - PAC- President’s speeches, correspondence to Board of Directors, Memorandum on current conditions in Poland, budget recommendations, correspondence with White House, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - PAC- Articles, Polish American Congress Charitable Foundation, statements and reports by president Mazewski, correspondence, various memorandums and bulletins, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - PAC- Electronic mail, reports of President Masewski, Board of Directors meetings, “Political Actions of Polish American Congress Since Martial Law in Poland”, correspondence with White House, PAC Charitable Foundation, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - PAC- Correspondence, Report on the Activities of the Washington PAC office, report of Executive Committee, documents concerning relations with Poland, PAC Charitable Foundation, Leadership Development Conference, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - PAC- Official ballot of amendment of the PAC by-laws (problem of individual membership vs. organization membership), 1984 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - PAC- Refugee and Immigration Committee, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence between Governor Ella Grasso and TWM- Multiculturalism Project, Ontario materials, newspaper clippings, 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - “Quo Vadis, Polish American Congress?” By E. Kusielewicz, in Pol-Am Journal, September, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Yale Committee and Cultural Relations with Poland- Polish week at Yale, November 13-21, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - PAC National- President's Carter visit to Poland and related correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - PAC National- Correspondence with The State Department, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Captive Nations Week- Official statement by Governor Ella Grasso, July 13-19, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Protest against destruction of the Orlat cemetary in Lwów by Soviet authorities, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Mt. St. Joseph Academy correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Democratic State Central Committee- Jefferson-Jackson Dinner, TWM participation, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Polish National Home- Talk delivered by Natunewicz, Chester F. talk, Hartford, May 2, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper clippings- Various topics, 1966-1980 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - "National Treasures of Poland" exhibit at Philadelphia Museum of Art, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - PAC National- Financial statements, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - PAC National- Membership statistics, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - PAC National- Anti-defamation activities, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - PAC National- Minutes of the Board of directors meeting, Chicago, Illinois, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - PAC other state divisions - General information, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - PAC Central & Northern New York District - Speech by TWM, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - PAC National- Reports from Board of Directors meeting, Buffalo, New York, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - PAC National- 200th anniversary of Pulaski's arrival in the USA - correspondence, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - PAC National- 200th anniversary of Pulaski's arrival in the USA - information, declaration, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - PAC National- 200th anniversary of Pulaski's arrival in the USA - newspaper coverage, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - PAC National- General correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - PAC National- Human rights in Poland, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - PAC National- Polonia in American politics, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - PAC National- Membership tally for Board of Directors, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - PAC National- Executive Committee meetings, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - PAC National- Reorganization Committee meetings, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - PAC National- Year end reports, 1976-1978 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - PAC National- Board of Directors meetings, 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - PAC district of Conn.- INS & Rene Albina treatment of Polish immigrants case - Senator Christopher Dodd, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - INS, Department of State- Senator Christopher Dodd correspondence and legal papers, 1981-1983 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - INS, State Department- Polish immigrants issue - news clippings, 1981-1985 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Suit vs. INS, attorney General & State Department- Correspondence & legal papers, 1981-1986 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Polish American Medical & Dental Association of American & National Advocates Society - Joint Convention, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - PNA District 2- Distinguished Service Award, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - US State Department reports on Implementation of Helsinki Final Act, 1979-1983 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Award of the Gold Medal of Honor, UNICO National - Joseph A. Zdunczyk, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Shettleski Ryszard - proklamacja, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 36)
- Democratic Party, Professional Assignments, Jobs
  - Democratic National Committee, Polish American Division- 1952 Elections- flyers, press releases, clippings. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Democratic Party campaigns- Correspondence, 1950-1956 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Democratic Polish Americans- Correspondence, newspaper clippings, “Rules of the Democratic Party of the State of Connecticut”, 1954-1962 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 1964 Elections- Correspondence, recommendations, contributions, flyers, clippings (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Democratic State Convention- Frank Kowalski for U.S. Senate- Speeches, correspondence, recommendations, newspaper clippings, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, telegrams, newspaper clippings regarding government and contributions to campaign funds, 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - 1968 Elections- Telegrams, correspondence. (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Former U.S. Ambassador to Poland John Gronouski's visit to Hartford, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - 1970 Elections- Correspondence, compilation of positions held on social issues, calendar of events, newspaper clipping regarding Julius Kremski, Emilio Daddario, or Joe Duffey. (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, acknowledgments of campaign contributions, newspaper clippings, 1969-1978 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - 1980 Presidential Election- Carter-Reagan- Flyers, correspondence, clippings. (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Windsor, CT Democratic Committee- (Chairman was TWM)- Correspondence about appointments, patronage jobs, etc., 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Windsor, CT Democratic Town Committee- Procedures, correspondence, party rules, handwritten notes, 1957-1964 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Windsor, CT Democratic Town Politics- Related documents, articles, charts, lists, 1956-1968 (Box 8, Folder 14)